mangaspot.com 2008-12-18

# MangaSpot - Our Privacy Policy

**MangaSpot.com is your #1 source for manga. We serve 60+ series, using direct downloads, including 3x3 Eyes, 666 Satan, Agharta, Air Gear, Ares, Battle Royale, Beck, Berserk, Black Cat, Blade of the Immortal, Bleach, Bowling King, Bremen, Cannon God Exx, Chaosic Rune, Chobits, Death Note, D. Gray Man, DNA2, Eyeshield 21, Flame of Recca, Freesia, Fruit Basket, Fullmetal Alchemist, Furi Kuri, Gantz, Golden Boy, Great Teacher Onizuka, H2, Hana Yori Dango, Hikaru No Go, Homunculus, Hot Gimmick, Houshin Engi, Hunter X Hunter, Ichiban!!!, Inuyasha, Katsu, Kimagure Orange Road, Lilim's Kiss, Love Hina, Mahou Sensei Negima, Maison Ikkoku, Naruto, One Piece, Orphen, Orphen Max, Parallel, Pastel, Pretty Face, Prince of Tennis, Ranma, Rave, Rookies, Rurouni Kenshin, School Rumble, Shaman King, Shamo, Slam Dunk, Team Medical Dragon, Tenjou Tenge, Tokko, Ultimate Hentai Kamen, Vagabond, White Dragon, Yakitate Japan, Yamato Gensouki, Yu Yu Hakusho, Zetman, Zombie Powder.**

---  
|    **•**Home   
  **•**[Contact Us](mailto:webmaster@mangaspot.com)   
  **•** Bookmark Us   
  **•**FAQs   
  **•**Staff   
  **•**Affiliation   
  **•**Links   
  **•**[ **Anime Streams**](http://anime.mangaspot.com/)   
  **•** **Forums**

  **•**+Anima   
  **•**20th Century Boys   
  **•**3x3 Eyes   
  **•**337 Byooshi   
  **•**666 Satan   
  **•**7 Seeds   
  **•**Addicted to Curry   
  **•**Agharta   
  **•**Ah! My Goddess   
  **•**Air Gear   
  **•**Aishiteruze Baby   
  **•**Akane-chan Overdrive   
  **•**Angel Densetsu   
  **•**Ares   
  **•**Battle Royale   
  **•**Beck   
  **•**Berserk   
  **•**Black Cat   
  **•**Blade of the Immortal  
  **•**Bleach   
  **•**Bowling King   
  **•**Bremen   
  **•**Buzzer Beater   
  **•**Cannon God Exx.   
  **•**Chaosic Rune   
  **•**Chobits   
  **•**Crayon Shin-chan   
  **•**D. Gray Man   
  **•**Death Note   
  **•**DearS   
  **•**Detective Conan   
  **•**DNA^2   
  **•**DragonBall*   
  **•**Eyeshield 21   
  **•**Flame of Recca   
  **•**Freesia   
  **•**Fruit Basket   
  **•**Fullmetal Alchemist   
  **•**FullMoon wo Sagashite  
  **•**Furi Kuri   
  **•**Gantz   
  **•**Girls Saurus   
  **•**Girls Saurus DX   
  **•**Golden Boy   
  **•**GTO   
  **•**H2   
  **•**Hajime no Ippo   
  **•**Hana Yori Dango   
  **•**Hikaru no Go   
  **•**Homunculus   
  **•**Hot Gimmick   
  **•**Houshin Engi   
  **•**Hunter X Hunter   
  **•**Ichiban!!!   
  **•**Ichigo 100%*   
  **•**Inuyasha   
  **•**Jiraishin   
  **•**Katsu   
  **•**Kimagure Orange Road  
  **•**Lilim's Kiss   
  **•**Love Hina   
  **•**Mahou Sensei Negima!  
  **•**Maison Ikkoku   
  **•**MAR   
  **•**Mr. Fullswing   
  **•**Naruto   
  **•**One Piece   
  **•**Orphen   
  **•**Orphen Max   
  **•**Parallel   
  **•**Pastel   
  **•**Ping Pong Club   
  **•**Pokemon Adventures   
  **•**Pretty Face   
  **•**Prince of Tennis   
  **•**Ranma 1/2   
  **•**Ragnarok   
  **•**Rave   
  **•**REAL   
  **•**Renka   
  **•**Rookies   
  **•**Rurouni Kenshin   
  **•**Ryuroden   
  **•**School Rumble   
  **•**Shadow Lady   
  **•**Shaman King   
  **•**Shamo   
  **•**Slam Dunk   
  **•**Suzuka   
  **•**Team Medical Dragon   
  **•**Tenjou Tenge   
  **•**Tokko   
  **•**Tough   
  **•**Tsubasa Chronicles   
  **•**Ultimate Hentai Kamen  
  **•**Vagabond   
  **•**Whistle!   
  **•**White Dragon   
  **•**Yakitate!! Japan   
  **•**Yamato Gensouki   
  **•**Yu Yu Hakusho   
  **•**Zetman   
  **•**Zombie Powder   
_   * - Updated Recently._

  **•**[AnimeA](http://www.animea.net/)   
  **•**[Anime Alliance](http://www.anime-alliance.com/)   
  **•**[Anime Capsule](http://animecapsule.net/)   
  **•**[Anime DL Center](http://www.adc-distro.com/)   
  **•**[Anime Downloadz](http://www.animedownloadz.com/)   
  **•**[Anime Element](http://anime-element.com/)   
  **•**[Anime Influenced](http://anime-influenced.com/)   
  **•**[Bleach Network](http://www.bleach-network.com/)   
  **•**[Deimon High](http://www.deimonhigh.com/)   
  **•**[Naruto HQ](http://www.narutohq.com/)   
  **•**[oz-anime](http://www.oz-anime.com/)   
  **•**[RawManga](http://www.rawmanga.com/)   
  **•**[Saiyan Island](http://www.saiyanisland.com/)   
  **•**[Shinigami Central](http://shinigamicentral.net/)

| 

****

### **_Privacy Policy_**

        MangaSpot.com respects the privacy of our visitors. Be assured that we will never share anyone's personal information with anyone else. This means your e-mail address, name, and location, hostname, or IP address will remain confidential. These data are collected for statistical reasons only and will not be distributed to any others. 

**Children's Privacy**   
MangaSpot.com does not knowingly collect personal data from children under the age of 13. We make reasonable efforts to prevent someone who is underage from joining as a member of MangaSpot.com, and will not collect information from them. If MangaSpot.com learns that a child under the age of 13 has become a member, we will close that child's account and delete any information collected about the child. Not withstanding the foregoing, MangaSpot.com may choose to retain some personal information such as the child's e-mail address as a means to prevent the child from re-registering at our website. The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) went into effect in April 2000, and as a result websites all over the world wide web had to change their standards to not collect any information from a child. 

**Disclosing Information**   
MangaSpot.com may store and disclose personal information allowed or required by applicable law or when deemed advisable by us. This means that we may make disclosures that are necessary to conform to legal and regulatory requirements or processes and to protect the rights, safety, and property of MangaSpot.com, users of the MangaSpot.com website, and the public. 

**Security**   
At MangaSpot.com we make reasonable efforts to protect personal information such as passwords and use technology such as encryption, access control procedures, firewalls, and physical security. We urge you to use a unique password with both letters and numbers to protect your account on MangaSpot.com and it's affiliated websites. If others, including family, friends or other household members access and use the message board through your login credentials, you are responsible for the actions of that individual. Only in extreme cases will your account be fully terminated. 

**Third Parties**   
Third Party websites may collect information from users of MangaSpot.com, this information will include your IP address, hostname, and information about your system to help us serve you better. These are purely used for statistical reasons, and will not be used in any way other then that. Some programs that may collect this information include: eXTReMe Tracking, Nedstat, and Webalizer. 

**Website Policy Changes**   
MangaSpot.com reserves the right to change this, and any other policy located on our website at anytime without notifying our users. By continuing to access MangaSpot.com and any of it's affiliated websites and files, you are agreeing to all of the terms as stated above on this document. You also hereby affirm that you are in compliance with all Federal, State and Local laws in your place of residence concerning the contents of MangaSpot.com. 

| 

:: **Donation Stats** ::   
\- Goal: $60   
\- Donated: $194.00   
\- Goal Reached!   
\- Month: February   
\- Donors

Thank you Donors!!   
  
---|---|---
